igeeksblog.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy for iGeeksBlog.com

The privacy of the visitors to iGeeksBlog.com is important to us.

At iGeeksBlog.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit iGeeksBlog.com, and how we safeguard your information. We will never sell your personal information, including your email address, to third parties.

* * *

###  **Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and a number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

* * *

###  **Cookies and Web Beacons**

iGeeksBlog.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

###  **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.iGeeksBlog.com
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.iGeeksBlog.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include… Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.iGeeksBlog.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

iGeeksBlog.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. iGeeksBlog’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

###  **Google Analytics Cookie**

We use Google Analytics to get insights into consumer demography, psychography/consumer behavior, traffic sources, and other necessary information. However, we do not share the same for any commercial purpose.

* * *

###  **Content Policy**

  * All the articles/contents published on iGeeksblog.com have been uniquely written by respected authors. Based on information found on the internet from various sources like material, news, videos, etc., articles are written after thorough research. In some cases, the information mentioned in the contents may vary as they may have been published a long time back. Hence, we request you to drop an email at igeeksblogs@gmail.com to change/update the content.
  * We reserved right to change the content, delete the content, delete the pages and information on this website anytime.
  * We believe the content presented here cannot be 100% accurate as well correct. It could vary from another source of information.

* * *

###  **Image Policy**

  * The images, shown in the article/content, contain the ownership of iGeeksBlog. The images, which are from third-party, are given credit passes to individual ownership. Images are used merely for the reference purpose.
  * If you have the ownership of the Images and do not want to let us use them; kindly email us at igeeksblogs@gmail.com to remove the same.

* * *

We care about the personal information you share online. At some points, iGeeksBlog collects personal information so please read the policies to make sure you understand our practices fully.

###  **Comment**

Email addresses are required for commenting and they are not published along with a comment. We do not share them with any third-party commenting tools for any commercial use.

###  **Newsletter Subscription**

Email addresses are required to join our newsletter subscription. Only verified email addresses with your prior consent will receive future updates from iGeeksBlog.

###  **Fill-Up Forms**

Name and Email address are required to contact iGeeksBlog for any queries or business inquiries. We use that personal information to contact you back for your query or business inquiries. We do not use this information for any other promotional activities or share with other third-party tools.

###  **Personal Information of Contest Participant**

We may ask for Name and Email address of contest participant. We may also ask for a contact number, residential address or other required personal information from contest winner to contact him/her and to deliver the prize.

Along with that iGeeksBlog.com is created for information purpose only. The information we have posted here is a best with our knowledge and collected from the web. The information might be wrong or out dated and Visitor will only responsible for his/her own decision.
